Guide to the Bruce T. Wilkins papers,1960-2002.
Wilkins, Bruce T. papers
- Aid for Designing Angler Surveys (AFDAS)- Correspondence, Notes and Manuals, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- AFDAS- Article, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- AFDAS- General Information, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- AFDAS Alpha Testers Version 0.1, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- AFDAS Beta Testers, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- AFDAS Progress Report, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- AFDAS Presentations and Papers, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Artificial Intelligence(AI) Applications- Paper, Development and Literature, 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Outdoor Recreation Curriculum, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Cornell Concepts of Outdoor Recreation Curriculum, 1968-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Video: "Instructions: CU Bass and Panfish Management-(Master Copy)" (VHS)-(no date) (Box 6, Folder 10)
- American Fisheries Society- Annual Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Cooperative Extension Program, 1988-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Daniel J. Decker- Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1985-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Daniel J. Decker- Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Staff Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- International Graduate Core (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Linking Project Background, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Program in Sustainable Management, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- NRES Policy Sub-Group (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Grading Information, 1970-1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Computer Committee, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- NRES 406, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- NRES 406, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Tompkins City Resource Development Committee, 1967-1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- 3 Week Agent School Aid (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Outdoor Recreation, 1963-1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Program Staffing, 1982-1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Sea Grant Extension In the Future (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Joint Concerns, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Renewable Resources Extension Act (RREA), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Planning 1994 Kick-Offs, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Sea Grant Senior Program Specialist (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Funding Opportunities, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- 4-H Information, 1983-1994 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Cornell Land Use Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Graduate Committees, Master of Professional Studies (MPS), Master of Environmental Management (MEM), 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Faculty Fellows, 1970-1994 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Teaching and Curriculum Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- NRES Extension Programs, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Internal Scanning, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Environmental Stewardship/Land Use, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Sustainable Agriculture Training, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Harry Everhart - Correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Faculty In-Residence Committee, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Career Patterns of Nine NY Sea Grant Extension Staff, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Bruce De Young Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- 4-H Environmental Issues, 1970-1996 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- NOAA Marine Advisory Service Conference, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Marine Advisory Fellowship, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Situation Statements, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Communications Assignment, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Executive Meeting Minutes, 1971-1986 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Bluefish Assignments, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- NRES 107- Prelim, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Agriculture Information, 1967-1997 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Fund Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Extension Staff and Faculty Meetings, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Department Extension- Staff Meetings and Minutes, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Bruce T. Wilkins - Prepared Talks, 1974-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Course Talks, 1970-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Isle of Shoals, 1974-1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- In Depth Study Week, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Arnot Forest Camp, 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Program Leaders Workshop, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Director's Report, 1973,1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- SEA/CR Review, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- NRES 107 Course Information, 1985-1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- NRES 107 Course Information, 1985-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- NRES 107 Course Information, 1985-1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- NRES 107 Grades Final, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- NRES 107 Grades, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- NRES 107 Final Exams etc, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- NRES 107 Lab 10, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- NRES 107 Lab 9 (Excel II) (Box 7, Folder 19)
- NRES 107 Last Lecture 29, Spring 1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- NRES 107 Lecture 27 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- NRES 107 Lecture 2 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- NRES 107 Lecture 20, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- NRES 107 Lecture 19, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- NRES 107 Lecture 20 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- NRES 3 Event 3, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- NRES 107 Lecture 12, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- NRES 107 Lecture 18 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- NRES 107 Quizzes, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- NRES 107 Lab 8, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- NRES 107 Fawn loss, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- NRES 107 Lecture 15, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- NRES 107 Lecture 14, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- NRES Lecture 13, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- NRES Lecture 16, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- NRES Lab 7 Excel I, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- NRES Lecture 12, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- NRES Lab 6 Event I, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- NRES 107 Lecture 3 Alberta, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- NRES Prelim I Period II, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- NRES 107 Lab 5, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- NRES 107 Lecture 10 Mark Bain Pop. Est., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- NRES 107 Lecture 9, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- NRES 107 Lab 5 and Guides for Antelope, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- NRES 107 Lecture 8, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- NRES 107 Lecture 7, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- NRES 107 Lecture 6, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- NRES 107 Lecture 5, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- NRES 107 Lab 2, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- NRES 107 Lecture 4, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- NRES 107 Lecture 2, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- NRES 107 Lab 1, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- NRES 107 Lecture 1, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- NRES 107 Events, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Washington Course NRES 401, Fall 1987 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Washington Course NRES 402 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Extension Program Visits, 1985-1994 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Washington Course, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Washington Ideas, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Proposal Refinement, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Advisory Service Projects, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Proposal Reviews, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- National Needs List, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Computer Committee Meetings, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Computer Committee Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Computer Committee Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- PC Users Group, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Resource Policy and Planning Faculty Search Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Resource Policy and Planning Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Resource Policy and Human Studies Group Memos, Minutes and Proposals, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Resource Policy and Human Studies Group Correspondence, Memos and Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- NRES 604, Spring 1978 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- NRES 604, Fall 1980 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Search Committee Asst. Prof. (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Animal (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Wilkins Correspondence, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- 42nd North American Wildlife and Natural Resource Conference, March 1977 1977 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- College Policy Committee CALS, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Recreation Sub-Committee of the Joint Natural Resources Committee Minutes, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 78)
- Extension Program Profile, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 79)
- Dept. of Environmental Conservation, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 80)
- NRES 40 Washington DC, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 81)
- Development Recreation (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Extension Forum, October 1988 (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Long Documents (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Association of Natural Resources Extension Professional Awards, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 85)
- Association of Natural Resources Extension Professional Awards, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 86)
- AFS Symposium, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- Natural Resource Environmental Management, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 88)
- Publications
- Publications by Wilkins, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Publications by Wilkins, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Publications by Wilkins, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Publications by Wilkins, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Publications by Wilkins, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Publications by Wilkins, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Publications by Wilkins, 1980s (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Publications by Wilkins, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 8)